[Episode 13]
I get how angry you feel,
but only by planning carefully
can we catch them all in one sweep.
I watched Yue die in front of me
with my own eyes.
How can I be calm?
Your Majesty, I'm here to escort you back...
I will think twice about what I do.
The Censorate will handle this case.
Your Majesty, you may return.
What do you plan to do next?
I need to know.
Otherwise, I'll be worried.
Since the gambling house
has already known my identity,
and Lv Da has a grudge against me,
they will certainly get back at me.
I believe they will come to me.
They will come to you for two reasons.
Either they rope you in,
or they take your life.
I will handle this myself.
You may go, Your Majesty.
- This way, please.
- Alright.
[Bofeng House]
Come again!
- I'll fetch Ms. Yan.
- Okay.
[May You Win]
[Bofeng House]
Ms. Yan, I'm Hao Wen Ming,
the major owner of Xingrong Gambling House.
Today, I've come to pay a visit
to Miss Meng.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Hao.
May I ask what you want
to see Miss Meng about?
Miss Meng is not someone
you can see as you wish.
Ms. Yan,
I came with the utmost sincerity
and generous benefits.
This kind of liquor was produced
in the extreme cold regions.
The brewing process is quite complex.
It tastes rich and mellow,
with a lingering aftertaste.
In the capital, only I can get it.
I can supply this liquor
exclusively to Bofeng House
at 30 percent below the market price.
If you find this agreeable,
we can consider this
as the start of our cooperation.
And you introduce me to Miss Meng.
What do you say?
It sounds quite interesting.
Honored guest,
please proceed to the second floor.
Madam.
What did you just hear from them?
Mr. Hao seems to have come
specifically to see Miss Meng.
It seems Miss Meng is handling a case
related to the Xingrong Gambling House.
I knew it.
There must be some shady dealings
between Yan Fu Zhi and Meng Ting Hui.
- Sure.
- Right now,
I'm going to write a complaint letter
to report them.
Miss Meng.
I've heard so much about you.
Seeing you today,
I finally understand what is gorgeous,
elegant, talented,
and knowledgeable lady like.
Meeting me today is an honor
you will take with you
to your family's grave.
No, I mean, meeting you is an honor
I'll take with me to my family's grave.
Don't get me wrong, please.
Upon seeing you,
I become somewhat incoherent.
Mr. Hao. You must be here for a reason.
What brings you here today?
I heard
you went to my gambling house last night.
I did not personally welcome you,
and you didn't enjoy yourself there.
I feel truly sorry.
Today, I came to apologize to you.
By the way, it's an honor for me
to be friends with you.
Miss Meng.
Open it.
This is of top-quality.
Look, this pearl is big and round.
You can spot good stuff.
Buddy.
This necklace is yours.
- No.
- Just take it.
Miss Meng and I are talking business.
If it works out, we will be like family.
Miss.
Wen Ming is quite sincere.
Consider what he said.
Two more.
Mr. Hao.
I heard your gambling house is backed
by some powerful figures.
Your business is not simple, isn't it?
Miss Meng.
You truly are well-informed.
To be honest with you,
indeed, some powerful figures
back our gambling house up.
But those are just small-time connections.
We need powerful figures like you
to back us up.
Miss Meng.
Please sit.
Once you sign this cooperation contract,
we will be on the same boat.
Since you want cooperation,
you need to be very frank with me.
What exactly is the business
on the second floor of your gambling house?
And what is the background
of those masked gamblers?
Miss Meng.
Secrets can only be shared
[Partner]
with those on the same boat.
As long as you sign it,
I guarantee I'll tell you all I know.
[Contract]
Miss Meng.
You're hesitating, so you do not trust me?
Are you unwilling to cooperate with me?
I am just thinking.
Just 20 percent of profits?
Is it worth me risking my official position?
No, it's not.
I need at least
- seven--
- 30 percent.
30 percent.
One percent less,
and our cooperation is off the table.
Miss Meng.
You're good at doing business.
Alright, 30 percent is okay then.
Get me a brush pen.
Miss Meng, I have thought again.
If you sign this contract,
I fear it could be a leverage against you.
- Get me a brush pen.
- Come on, buddy.
[Meng Ting Hui]
Quite straightforward, Miss Meng.
Mr. Hao.
So, can you answer my questions now?
Sure, since we're on the same boat now,
let's talk over drinks.
Bottoms up.
On the second floor,
some special guests need special hospitality.
You know what I mean, huh?
Yeah, of course.
- Drink.
- Drink, buddy.
- Cheers.
I have heard
that the semi-monthly Flower Feast
is very wonderful.
Buddy.
Buddy, come.
My good buddy.
I also want to go to the Flower Feast
to broaden my horizons.
Normally, since we are on the same boat,
going up to the second floor
should not be a problem.
But...
What are you looking for, buddy?
Tomorrow's Flower Feast
is not held on our second floor.
It is at our gang leader's Spring Manor
on the western outskirts of the city.
That is not open to ordinary people.
Even if you want to go, you have to wait.
Buddy.
Your gang leader is truly mysterious.
The last time I saw him, he almost killed me.
As the saying goes,
out of blows friendship grows.
Come on, let's drink.
Buddy.
Miss Meng.
What is your gang leader's name?
Ling Yun Fei.
Fei.
She is just a greedy female official.
Since she signed the contract,
she will have to do what I say.
Master, Meng Ting Hui signed the contract.
She won't be able to interfere
[Meng Ting Hui]
with our business anymore.
Rest assured,
Master.
These officials
appear righteous on the surface,
but are corrupt and scheming inside.
They fear exposure the most.
Over these years,
we have used contracts
to control many officials in the capital.
It seems Meng Ting Hui
is nothing special at all.
Meng Ting Hui almost died at my hands,
but she didn't look afraid.
And you handled her with just a drink?
More than just a drink.
I also gave her
a large box of gold, silver, and jewels.
She also gets 30 percent
of the gambling house's profits.
You are quite generous.
How many secrets did you reveal to her
after you got drunk?
Miss Meng, be careful.
The place for Flower Feast
is even more remote than I imagined.
Miss Meng, don't worry.
As long as we follow Hao Wen Ming's carriage,
we'll locate the feast.
Miss Meng, His Majesty has not yet replied
to our memorial.
Our acting without authorization
is already exceeding our authority.
Here you go again.
If we wait for His Majesty's reply,
it will be too late.
If you are afraid, just go back.
If I were afraid, I would not be here.
I work in the Censorate by imperial decree
and act by law,
while you only know how to play petty,
self-defeating tricks.
Self-defeating tricks?
Listen, laws mean nothing
to the Huxiao Gang.
Stop arguing. Just play it by ear.
Let's follow the carriage first,
but be sure to keep our distance.
No!
Get away!
You're indeed smart.
According to our guards,
Meng Ting Hui has gone to the Spring Manor
with two of her trusted persons.
Everything is under your control.
How many secrets did you reveal to her
after you got drunk?
Master, don't worry,
just small talk with her the whole time.
I also set her up.
I deliberately revealed a fake place
for the Flower Feast.
Even if she goes,
it will be a wild goose chase.
That is not enough.
If she comes,
I will make sure she never returns.
He abandoned the carriage. Well...
Has he arrived?
Go take a look.
Miss Meng.
Run!
Is the amount of gunpowder enough?
Sure, Master.
We will definitely blast them to dust.
I heard that Xiyan flowers
are popular in Beijian.
Many musicians often use this flower
as an adornment.
So I had them decorate the banquet
with these flowers.
Are you happy with it?
We appreciate Your Majesty's kindness.
But Beijian is bitterly cold all year round.
We have always prized the snow lotus.
So this kind of Xiyan flower
is not commonly seen.
I see.
No wonder many of the treasures
your country offered this time
are all exquisitely carved
with snow lotus patterns.
Now I understand.
By order of our lord,
we've come to visit Your Majesty.
We wish that Beijian
and the Ning Empire will forever be allied.
We also wish
to be good neighbors with Beijian
and stabilize the borders together.
Zhi Li.
Miss Meng.
Miss Meng, you are injured.
I have medicine.
Are you alright?
Yin Qing, are you okay?
I'm fine.
My superficial wound is nothing serious.
This carriage was not heading
to the Spring Manor at all.
But now, how do we get to the Flower Feast?
I know where it really is now.
Master.
Stop!
Don't move!
Don't move! Kneel!
You bunch of wretches!
Miss Meng, buddy.
Are you trying to destroy my place?
Hao Wen Ming,
you rely on the power of the Huxiao Gang,
using gambling as a front
to traffic women.
Now we've caught you red-handed.
Miss Meng, you're slandering innocent people.
We are just hosting a banquet.
And they just played a little game.
A little game?
Treating women shamefully
is what you call a little game?
Miss Meng, don't be so angry.
We are all on the same side.
You wish!
Miss Meng is a woman of integrity.
How dare you slander her!
Buddy, how can you turn your back on me?
- The other day, I gave you an expensive--
- Shut up!
- Arrest them!
- Wait!
This is outrageous!
Right under the Emperor's nose,
there is such an immoral affair.
You came at the perfect time.
Mr. Zheng.
These wretches--
I've received a report from civilians
that Meng Ting Hui has accepted bribes
and gathered a crowd for lewd activities.
I am here specifically to investigate it.
Lewd activities?
Miss Meng is here handling a case.
There must be a misunderstanding.
I've already sent people to Bofeng House
to search and find the illicit goods.
Whether there is a misunderstanding or not,
we will know soon enough.
[Bofeng House]
Hurry up!
Sirs, what has happened?
- Search!
- Yes!
Wait! What are you doing?
Listen to me, Mr. Zheng.
Meng Ting Hui bullied me with her power.
She forced me to sign a contract
to take 30 percent
of my gambling house's profits.
She threatened that if I didn't comply,
she would make trouble for my gambling house.
Hao Wen Ming.
You're just slandering me.
Mr. Zheng, please look at this.
It is written in black and white.
It has Meng Ting Hui's signature on it.
What?
Mr. Hao, where is my signature?
How dare you slander an official!
Miss Meng, Mr. Hao must not be sober yet.
Are you messing with me?
Mr. Hao, you gave her
a box of gold, silver, and jewels.
Right, I gave her a box of jewels.
She also extorted a box of jewels
from me as a deposit.
Sir, these are the illicit goods
we found at Bofeng House.
This is the evidence.
Mr. Zheng, please seek justice for us.
This is my private property,
not illicit goods.
Nonsense!
You are a lowly sixth-rank official
and just took office.
Where would you get so much money?
It was a gift from her good friend, Ms. Yan,
to thank Miss Meng for devising strategies
to manage Bofeng House.
Nonsense! This was all mine!
Let me tell you,
this box is specially made
by our gambling house.
It's engraved
with the seal of my gambling house.
Do you dare to let them check?
Why check my superior's property?
Aren't you just acting like a hooligan?
It's ridiculous to determine ownership
based solely on the seal.
I do not accept it.
You are totally unreasonable.
If the bottom of the box is engraved
with the seal of my gambling house,
then it is my stuff.
If it is engraved with Bofeng House's seal,
then it is yours.
Are you afraid now?
Move aside!
Get your hands off!
Sir, please check it out.
What?
[Bofeng House]
Mr. Hao.
You just said
this stuff belongs to the owner
of the seal engraved
on the bottom of the box.
Mr. Zheng, soldiers,
you have also seen with your own eyes.
The bottom of this box is engraved
with the seal of Bofeng House.
So naturally, it is Miss Meng's stuff.
Hao Wen Ming.
From the moment you handed over the contract,
you already lost.
I have played along with you.
Are you satisfied?
Meng Ting Hui.
You...
Mr. Zheng, don't listen to her.
She must have tampered with evidence.
You must seek justice for us.
Meng Ting Hui, you have always acted oddly.
It's difficult to clear your suspicion
with just a few words from your side.
Come back with me to the Supreme Court.
If you are innocent,
I will naturally let you go.
The Supreme Court has no right
to interfere with the Censorate's cases.
If you want to interrogate me,
you'll have to let me escort the criminals
to the Censorate first.
I am acting by law.
Why should I listen to you?
That man is wearing a red jade ring
on his thumb,
carved with a caged bird on it.
You are the one who brutally murdered Yue!
You colluded with Hao Wen Ming
and these gamblers
who participated in the Flower Feast.
Today, you did not come sincerely
to investigate the case.
You came for me.
Meng Ting Hui, stop talking nonsense!
Yue's testimony is at the Censorate.
If you deny it,
we can confront it on the spot.
You're just a lowly sixth-rank official.
What can you do to me?
[Censorate]
Open your eyes and see.
This is a token bestowed by His Majesty.
Between you and me,
if only one person can leave alive,
it will certainly be me.
Divine Guard, heed my command!
Anyone who interferes will be executed
on the spot!
His Majesty has come.
Unmask these wretches!
Yes!
Isn't this Mr. Liu from the Hanlin Academy?
I didn't expect to see you here.
Mr. Shen, you mistook me for someone else.
Isn't this Vice Minister Zhang
from the Ministry of Revenue?
These guys also look quite familiar.
What a group of sanctimonious scourges.
Since you are all so afraid
to show your true faces,
then let them be paraded in these outfits,
from the gambling house to the prison.
Let the people of the capital see
what kind of brute wretches they are.
Throw Mr. Zheng and his men
into the prison immediately
for judgment.
Move!
You two, don't just kneel there.
Your Majesty.
May we send these women to the Censorate?
You're in charge of this case.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Yin Qing.
Get up. It's over now.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Well played, Miss Meng.
You're becoming better at cheating.
So, will you confess honestly?
Or shall I...
Stop pretending.
There are only the two of us here.
If you keep pretending,
you might really have to sleep
until tomorrow morning.
Your Majesty, I made huge mistakes.
My first mistake was not reporting
to Your Majesty in advance.
But it was because it was urgent,
and I didn't want to miss a good opportunity.
My second mistake
was accepting Hao Wen Ming's stuff.
But I was by no means greedy for money.
It was only to gain his trust.
And I did not actually sign that contract.
That's all, Your Majesty.
In that case,
you didn't make any mistake.
Instead, you made a perfect plan.
Even the timing of sending Zhi Li
to bring reinforcements
was calculated without the slightest error.
This allowed me
to witness it with my own eyes.
I'm impressed by the friendship
between you and Ms. Yan.
You even adamantly claimed
that black is white,
and that the corrupt is clean.
I never expected you
to have the potential to be a bad official.
So His Majesty knew all along.
Get up and speak.
I wonder
if I had not arrived in time today,
how would you have ended this?
I had the Divine Guard.
Has the Divine Guard already become yours?
Naturally, they belong to Your Majesty.
The money from the Huxiao Gang
also belongs to Your Majesty,
not under any supervision of Lord Xu.
Your Majesty can spend it at will.
Great.
It seems you can now earn money for me.
You even use money to keep my mouth shut,
leaving me with no way to blame you.
I humbly beg Your Majesty to forgive me once.
Those women wanted to leave their hometowns
by their own efforts.
They are educated and reasonable,
only wishing to serve the country.
It's heart-wrenching
to see them suffer so much.
I must seek justice for them.
I beg Your Majesty.
I have never said I would blame you.
Yet you are asking for forgiveness now.
Alright, stop pretending. Get up.
Meng Ting Hui.
You have a fever,
yet you still try to act tough.
You are selfish and self-interested,
full of lies.
After being exposed, you try to argue.
You're good at playing innocent
and pitiful.
You're so cunning, deceitful,
and duplicitous.
How do I know you are not deceiving me?
You really have a deep impression of me.
Are you proud of bullying a woman like me?
If you deceive me, you'll be dead.
You jinx.
Don't come back, you shameless person.
This time, we are completely even.
So you have such a well-behaved side.
Miss Meng, the medicine is ready.
Your Majesty.
It's so late, and you are still here.
Why have you come so late?
Without even knocking on the door.
Your Majesty, Miss Meng was injured today
and was also frightened
after being taken hostage.
So I brewed a bowl of decoction for her.
Let her drink it when she wakes up tomorrow.
You may leave now.
But...
Yes.
Wait.
I saw that you were also injured today.
Thank you for your hard work.
Rest early.
So Your Majesty cares about me.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Director of Censorate, Meng Ting Hui,
has uncovered Huxiao Gang's gambling house.
She has saved countless female students
and eradicated treacherous officials.
Her achievements are outstanding.
She is hereby specially promoted
to be a fifth-rank official
as a commendation.
Also, the members of the Censorate
should be rewarded
to honor their merits.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Many families
were broken
because of gambling.
The Xingrong Gambling House is involved
in countless acts of evil.
They trafficked women
and roped in court officials.
They've brought calamity to the people,
as a great scourge for the country.
I hope Your Majesty will protect all women
and prevent such tragedies
from happening again.
That's what I intend to do.
Chief Steward You.
Attention.
Effective immediately,
anyone who traffics in human beings,
once verified,
regardless of being the principal
or an accessory,
shall be beheaded immediately.
Their family property shall be confiscated.
Their clansmen shall be exiled 3,000 li.
All prefectures must strengthen patrols
to prevent trafficking and fraud.
If there is any negligence,
it will be severely punished without mercy.
Furthermore,
all gambling is banned in the Ning Empire.
Anyone who operates a gambling house
shall be beheaded.
And their accomplices
shall be flogged 100 times
and exiled 1,000 li.
Participants in gambling
shall be flogged 800 times
and fined 100 taels of silver.
All prefectures must strictly investigate
and handle relevant cases.
Anyone who covers it up
shall also be punished.
Thank you, Miss Meng,
for saving us from dire straits.
Thank you, Miss Shen.
Thank you, all of you.
All of you,
don't mention it.
We have already reported to the court
to secure compensation for you all.
For those who wish to return home,
we'll provide travel expenses.
For those who wish to stay in the capital,
we'll arrange proper settlement.
If you have the ambition
to take the Imperial Exam,
the Censorate is willing to recommend you.
The Censorate is your strong backing.
Miss Meng.
Although I have suffered a lot,
I still want to take the Imperial Exam
to obtain a scholarly rank like you
and be a good official.
I'm from a remote frontier town.
Local women are mostly trapped
in their homes.
I wish to return to my hometown and teach.
I want women to know
that they can also blaze their own trails.
It is indeed harder for women
to live in this world than men.
But as long as you have hope,
you'll dispel the clouds and see the sun.
We are relieved to see
that you have such aspirations.
Studying can certainly give people hope.
Thank you, Miss Meng.
Thank you, Miss Shen.
Both of you are models for women.
You're in big trouble.
Yet you're actually playing this.
Brother, are you so anxious
because you're afraid of being implicated?
Hao Wen Ming is now being cross-examined
under torture in Censorate.
How long do you think
he can hold out before he talks?
If he dares to utter even a single word,
I will kill his whole family.
If you don't restrain yourself,
the Divine Guard will come next time.
How formidable you look.
When you used my business involving beauties
to pave the way for your own promotion,
why didn't I see you show any mercy?
Now that the scandal is exposed,
you want to kick down the ladder.
The gambling ban makes me lose a fortune.
There is no way to let this go.
You are utterly crazy.
Do you want to sacrifice me
for your gain again?
Over the years,
[Account book]
all your dirty money has been recorded.
The Censorate will certainly be interested.
Don't worry.
I value family ties more than you do.
After all, you are my only blood relative.
Regarding the past incident,
I am sorry to you.
But I had no other choice back then.
Although you and I were not born
of the same mother,
when you were pinned in the mud,
crying for help,
and calling me brother,
I have remembered it for 20 years.
Do you think the Huxiao Gang
has come this far by sheer luck?
So now,
can you invalidate the gambling ban?
I will do my utmost to maneuver in the court.
But you must restrain yourself a bit.
For now,
don't make a move against Meng Ting Hui.